Enyaba, there's something
I'd like to ask you.
What does it mean to live?
It's to obtain all that one desires.
If you were to distill life into its
essence, that is what it would be.
A lust for riches, a desire for
fame, food, love, and lovers.
That is life's goal.
But one must always fight
to get what one wants.
Isn't that correct, Enyaba?
Indeed.
And if the battle is lost and one
fails to obtain what one desires most,
the result is frustration,
pain, and a sense of failure.
One carries the wound into the
future, into the next fearful battle.
I believe conquering that fear once
and for all is what it means to live.
The one who stands at the pinnacle
is the one who has no fear.
Do you understand, Enyaba?
I was the one who told you about the
existence of your stand and how to use it.
Also, you have an immortal body.
Is there anything you could possibly fear?
Perhaps, old woman. Hmm.
What burdens you, my lord?
The Joestar bloodline.
Hmm? Joestar?
They worry you?
Those worms are mere trash.
Your enemies are no match
for your stand. Yes,
but I must believe it's
destiny when the lives of
those worms are so thoroughly
entangled with mine.
It is a fate that has been written
for us all from the very beginning.
Let me be clear.
It is not the Joestars that I fear,
but the fact that I can never
underestimate their bloodline.
In order to obliterate all fear,
I have decided that I must remove
the Joestars from the cogs of fate.
You want to go and eliminate
them yourself simply
because you feel that they
cannot be underestimated?
Yes.
Foolishness!
You should never engage
in such trivial matters.
They are beneath someone of your stature.
I have sent seven stand-users
to command. The Empress,
the Wheel of Fortune, the Hangman, and
Temperance, the Emperor, and the Devil.
All of them on the move and ready
to strike whenever you call.
Thanks to these allies, you need not
take any action yourself, Lord Dio.
Let's go.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
A freighter!
I didn't see it at all!
Jotaro, something's
bothering you, isn't it?
Are you worried there might be
another stand user on this freighter?
It's not ideal, but we could handle it.
Not quite.
Strange they lowered the stairs.
But there's not a single soul
to be seen around here anywhere.
This ship came all this way to rescue us.
There has to be some
sort of crew on board.
Even if they're all stand
users, I'm getting on this boat.
I'm done drifting in circles.
Take my hand, kid.
I'll help you get up.
Good grief.
Hey, what's with this ship?
There's no captain in the control room?
There's no engineer in the radio room?
There's no one anywhere!
And yet, look at this!
All the gauges and machinery are
working properly, just like normal!
Maybe they're just all in the
bathroom with a bad case of the rugs!
Hey!
Isn't anyone around?
You have to see this!
Come here, quick!
Huh?
An ape!
There's an ape inside that cage!
It's an orangutan who the
hell cares about a friggin ape
let's split up and find whoever's
been feeding this thing?
Well, it doesn't appear
to be broken, but...
Avdol!
That's Sailor!
Watch out!
Oh, good grief.
That isn't any way to greet a lady
you've never met before now, is it?
But no one was touching the controls!
I saw that crane move, even though
there was no one operating it.
I don't believe in
ghosts, but what the hell?
I saw it too!
The crane impaled him all on its own!
Keep your guard up.
There's someone hostile here. Hey!
Don't touch the machinery.
You got that?
If it moves or runs on electricity!
Don't lay a finger on it!
If you want to live, then
you'll do exactly as I tell you!
Understand!
Get into the cabin below and stay
there until I tell you otherwise!
Did any one of you see even a
glimpse of a stand just now?
I didn't.
My apologies.
I was the closest to the
crane and yet I felt nothing.
I should have been able to send something!
All right!
I'll send Hierophant Green to
take a look around the ship!
I have no idea what's going on!
But scary things keep happening!
Whenever you guys are around!
Could you guys be jinxed?
I've heard about people who cause
disasters that endanger everyone?
But if that's what you
are, I'd better stay away.
I have just one bit of truth
for you, so listen closely.
Whatever happens, we're on your side.
Stay safe.
Make sure you stay with
the others, got it?
Let's go.
Do you want me to open the cage for you?
But I can't.
I have no idea where the key is.
And you're too big to let out.
You're giving me an apple?
But it doesn't make any sense.
This apple's been cut with a knife, and
the color hasn't really changed yet.
It looks totally fresh.
Like it was cut a second ago.
So, I guess there really must be
someone hiding somewhere on this boat.
Where is the person who feeds you?
Has he gone off and left you here?
Huh?
Whoa, you're a pretty smart monkey.
Who trained you to do that?
No way!
A monkey like you is
actually into looking at...
pin-ups of girls?
Hey kid be careful there
they say an orangutan
has five times the
strength of a normal human?
So it could easily rip
off your arm come on
stay with us in the
room on the other side!
Don't go off by yourself oh okay.
It's inconceivable.
I've had Hierophant Green
search every inch of this ship,
but I can't find a single
sign of human life aboard.
We've searched every pipe and crevice,
but still came up empty-handed.
Anything?
It's no use.
I can't get a connection.
Well, try again, damn it.
Gross.
I feel sticky from the salt water.
Huh?
Yeah, yeah,
yeah,
yeah
Ahh...
Huh?
Oh, my God.
Hey!
Jojo!
Take your lock, you stinking ape!
Seems at the same.
Isn't your run-of-the-mill monkey?
Could it be that he's the one?
Wait, who the hell ripped out that fan?
Had to be him!
So this ape's a stand user,
but where's the stand?
I should be able to see the
damn thing, but I can't!
It doesn't make any sense!
What the...
The steel propeller bent
on its own like it's alive!
Jojo!
Hey, what's going on here?
Son of a bitch!
There's no stand in sight
and somehow the window broke?
Star Platinum!
What's with this thing?
The ape just sank into
the wall and disappeared.
Hey, you saw that, right?
Stay close to me.
Something bad is going down.
The ape vanished into the wall.
But that orangutan has
to be the stand user.
When I touched it earlier, I felt
a stand's energy coming from it.
I have no doubt that he's
the one we're looking for.
Doesn't make any sense.
Why can't I see this
stand like I always do?
Wait.
What if I'm seeing it already?
What's happening?
Whoa, what's going on?
This isn't good.
It's swallowing us.
Is the freighter trying to...
Is it possible the ship itself is?
So the stand is actually the freighter.
Damn, you son of a...
All of it!
This ship itself and everything
on it is a gigantic stand!
The entire ship?
So there are stands that non-stand users
like that girl and the
crew members can see?
The only possible explanation
for that is that its immense
energy is making it possibly
seen with the naked eye.
But all this must demand a tremendous
amount of energy to operate.
A stand as huge as this!
Kick, send Hierophant Green to Jotaro.
He can help get us out of this.
I can't do that.
It's got a firm hold on
my stand that I'm stuck.
This is what it means to face
death We fell for this trap
and now we're hopelessly
ensnared with no way to escape.
The pressure keeps increasing at this rate
our bodies are going to be pulverized!
Will be damn we were careless.
We've got to
The word that the orangutan
was pointing to was strength.
It means force, energy, power, or aid.
And it is the eighth
card of the tarot deck.
It suggests challenge, a
strong will, and hidden powers.
Damn ape.
Thinks he's won already, huh?
This entire ship is my
stand, and you've lost!
You're totally outmatched and helpless!
And there's nothing you can do!
Jotaro needed no explanation.
He knew exactly what the ape was saying!
Aaaaaaahhhhhh!
Over here, monkey.
That button's not part of your stand.
Are you angry?
I guess it wounded your pride, since
you thought you'd already beaten us.
Oh, it's not hurt at all, is it?
Because apes like you
don't have any pride.
That's exactly what makes
you an ape and not a man.
What's going to hurt now is your head.
Good grief.
I've heard that when
frightened animals show their
stomachs to signal their
submission to the enemy.
So you're asking me to forgive you?
I'm afraid your actions have already
gone beyond the rules of the jungle.
So I don't think so.
What the...
the pipes and walls are distorting!
The whole ship is twisting up!
Hey, be surprised about it later.
This ship is about to sink.
It's time to leave.
Get back to the lifeboats.
Wow, I can't believe it.
The ship's shape is changing.
It's turning into a shabby little boat.
If I hadn't seen it myself,
I wouldn't believe it.
That ape was traveling
the sea on his own stand.
What terrifying power.
That was the first time I've
encountered such energy.
Hate to say it, but we were
completely overwhelmed this round.
If Jotaro hadn't figured it out,
we would have been done for.
Are we going to encounter even more stands
with crazy unknown powers from now on?
We'll have to be ready for anything.
Hey, you want some gum?
So, we're going to be
drifting again. Good grief.
My cigarettes are soaked.
There'll be plenty of sun and
time for them to get dry, Jojo.
We'll have to pray that we get
rescued and reach Singapore safely.
And soon.
It's been four days since we left Japan.
There are 46 days until time
runs out for the Joestars.
My lord, it would appear that
strength has been defeated.
But have no fear.
The remaining six stand users are all very
powerful and each deadlier than the last.
And one of them is my son.
His right arm shall crush our enemies.
The Joestars will not pose a threat
when he's finished with them.
You are a strange old woman.
What is it that you desire the most?
Oh, but I've told you many times.
My only wish is to stay
by your side, my lord.
Your guardian spirit
has unbelievable power.
Your ability to escape trouble and your
strange life are the result of that.
I would like to see your life unfold.
It's the only thing I want.
Once upon a time,
there was a prince from the land of Sumatra
who traveled the seas seeking new lands.
Eventually,
he happened upon an island
inhabited by lions called Sinks,
an island he named Singapore.
Today, it's straights bustle with ships
and tankers from around the world.
This nation that shares
both Western and Eastern
heritage thanks to free
trade is Tropical Singapore.
Good grief, we finally
made it to dry land.
We'll clean up and get
some rest at a hotel.
Once we've recharged, we'll
figure out our route to Egypt.
Alright, let's stay at that one.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If you move too quick, go away.
They're falling down like a domino.
All the buzzer men by the Nile.
They got the money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
Oh-eh-oh.
They snapped their
teeth on your cigarette.
Foreign types with a hookah. I say.
Oh-eh-oh.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop your drink then
they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of folks.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings.
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say.
Walk like an Egyptian.
Couldn't you guys at least give us a
chance to rest, persistent bastard?
She'll be in danger if she stays with us?
Polareff must have fallen
for Soul Sacrifices' trick!
Train! Tour!
Who's among us all?
Joestar, you bastard!